
【つみ式紲星あかり】



※使用上の注意

・ここに書いていないことでなにかやりたいことがあったら事前にご相談ください。
　Please contact us in advance if you have anything to do with something that is not mentioned here.

・このモデルはMikuMikuDance用のモデルデータです。
　基本的にはMikuMikuDance内でご利用下さい。
　VRChatへの転用はダメです。
　This model is model data for MikuMikuDance.
　Please use basically in MikuMikuDance.
　Diversion to VRChat is not good.

・このモデルは株式会社AHS様の「VOICEROID2紲星あかり」の二次創作です。
　関係者様に迷惑がかかるようなことがあれば配布を停止させて頂きます。
　This model is secondary creation of "VOICEROID2 紲星あかり" by AHS Corporation.
　Distribution will be suspended if there is any inconvenience to the stakeholders concerned.
　
・モデルについての問い合わせはモデル製作者までご連絡ください。
　Please contact me for inquiries about the model.

・このモデルの個人サイト・動画サイトなどでの使用は自由ですが、商用利用・再配布は禁止させて頂きます。
　個人的な改造などは自由ですが改造モデルの配布などの際は事前にご連絡ください。
　Use of this model at personal sites, movie sites, etc. is free.
　Commercial use / redistribution is not permitted
　Personal modifications are free.
　Please contact us beforehand when you want to distribute remodeled models.

・このモデルを使用して発生したいかなる損害・損失・トラブル・その他の不利益に対して当方は責任を持てません。
　自己責任の元、ご使用ください。
　I am not responsible for any damage, loss, trouble or other disadvantage that occurred using this model.
　Please use under the responsibility of self-responsibility.

・版権元やその他の関係者に迷惑をかけたり気分を害するような使用や、政治的目的・誹謗中傷目的などでの使用などは厳禁です。
　場を弁えたご利用をお願いします。
　It is not good to use such as bothering the copyright or other stakeholders or feeling offended.
　It is useless to use for political purposes, slander wounds, etc.

・この利用規約は予告なく変更される場合があることをご了承ください。
　Please understand that this terms of service may change without notice.


・お願いグーグル翻訳！なので英語が正しくなくても許して
　Please Google Translate! So even if English is not right, please forgive me



モデル製作：つみだんご


更新履歴
H30/08/06　　　　　　　　ver.0.8　　公開
H30/11/18　　　　　　　　ver.1.0　　ジャケット追加
　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　顔の造形を調整、物理の調整